This is I've Made Three Million Dollars With
My Thirty-Six Startups, by Marc Lou. Read by
a voice clone of Marc Lou. Monday,
September 7th, 2026
Today is a special day for me. I've
made 3 million dollars with my 36 startups.
Solo. 85 percent
margin. Bootstrapped. It
took 10 years, and I loved every second
of it. Here's my story. Here's
the chart: just over 3 million dollars earned
across the startups.
Chapter 1. Mark Zuckerberg Aura.
I graduated in Computer Science in 2016.
My friends applied for a job in Paris,
but it didn't feel right to me. My
exchange semester in Hong Kong in 2015
transformed me. I didn't know what I
wanted—I just didn't want that. On a regular
hangover Sunday morning, around two in the afternoon.
I watched The Social Network movie and had
an epiphany: I will be the next Mark
Zuckerberg. My secret unicorn
idea? Tinder for sports lovers.
I spent an entire year: Learning
to code because I was partying instead of
studying at the university. Asking people
to sign an NDA to listen to my
idea. Designing a logo and business cards.
I was making 10 dollars an hour and
believed I was Mark Zuckerberg. To pay the
bills, I was a waiter in a restaurant
in Paris. During my shift, a customer mentioned
a new school to learn entrepreneurship. I
was lonely, so I registered. The
teacher asked how my startup would make money.
I froze. How come I didn't think about
it after a year of work? My app
was a disaster. Users
couldn't even sign up. And I was the
only user. My relationship with my girlfriend
wasn't working either. On March 10th,
2017, I quit everything. The next
week, my parents drove me to the airport.
I cried in the car. My friend, Sacha,
was waiting for me in Seoul, South Korea.
We raised 100,000 dollars from angel
investors and built an AI startup with 2
employees. Here's a photo of Sacha and me
at Campus Seoul, a Google space. We were
trying to reverse-engineer flight ticket pricing to
predict future prices. 9 months later, we had
a bad product, no income, and I was
wearing a shirt every day. So I
quit, again. In December
2017, I was broke, in a foreign country,
and had zero self-confidence. I started to
smoke again I smoked for 7 years in
university and stopped when I arrived in Korea
After reflection, a pattern started to emerge: Big
goals, big failures. I saw an ad on
Facebook selling gloves for couples 1 big
mitten to hold hands together I decided to
copy and sell them on Facebook for Koreans.
As a product-obsessed engineer, I didn't think about
dropshipping. I had to build the product.
A lovely Korean grandma knitted 50 Glovers:
Gloves for Lovers I was quite proud of
the name It took a month and a
half to knit 50 Glovers. My new Korean
girlfriend helped with the translation. I burned
all of my savings on Facebook Ads a
few hundred dollars with this video. I
made 0 sales. In January
2018, my 8-square-meter bedroom was filled with
Glovers, but my bank account was empty. At
20 dollars per piece, I had to sell
them to pay the rent. My girlfriend and
I went down the street every night to
sell them. To brave the minus 15 degrees
Korean winter, we had to drink 1 liter
of beer before standing in the street for
2 hours. We would sell 2 gloves per
day. I would wake up sick and coughing.
What the fuck I am doing with my
life? Chapter 2.
She said "Yes". In April 2018, I
was more broke than ever, out of shape,
and unhealthy. I needed a big
change. Marc in April 2018, before
changing his exercise habits. I
applied for a second acting role to pay
the bills. I would get a call once
or twice a week and get paid 200
dollars per gig. Then I started to work
out every 2 days for clarity of mind—20
minutes of intense jumping rope. I got
shredded in 1 month. Finally, I
set a simple goal: Make 1 dollar online
with code. To avoid another failure, I
focused on problems, not products. Every
business wants to grow. So I decided to
build a gamified marketing tool for escape rooms.
At a startup event, I met Andrey, a
talented marketer who became my friend. He
said: Why don't you sell it before you
make it? I'm an engineer. I
love building. Marketing? Not at
all. But I failed for 2 years, so
I decided to listen. He taught me the
foundation of marketing. After a few cold emails,
Daniela from Time's Up Escape Rooms in Australia
wanted to learn more about the product over
a quick call. Marc taking a selfie in
his small bedroom in Korea. On Friday
13th, 2018, I was in Osaka, Japan for
a 3-day visa run. I just had a
bad night of sleep in the cheapest guest
house I could afford. Nine in the morning.
I was in the common area, it was
hot, and the wifi was bad. The call
started. There are no words to describe
how cringe I was. So here's the intro
of the sales pitch. After 42 minutes,
she said yes. By the end of the
day, she subscribed to the 99 dollars monthly
plan. Yes! I went back to
Korea and built the product. That call started
a SaaS business called VirallyBot. It made
about 100,000 dollars Here's a photo of thirty
thousand dollars in an old PayPal account. 1
call paid the bills for 5 years.
Chapter 3. Growing a SaaS.
After making my first 1 dollar online in
2018, my Korean girlfriend and I had no
reason to stay in Seoul anymore. We'd rather
be somewhere hot and cheap. So we moved
to Bali in September. I was working
on VirallyBot: a gamified marketing tool for
escape room businesses, priced at 199 dollars a
month. A typical day would be:
Marketing in the morning: Collecting leads and sending
cold emails. I tried cold calls, but it
was not working for me. Product in the
afternoon: Adding games and features while learning
how to code. We lived in Canggu with
2 roommates. Life was good.
I was not living in a bug-infested room
anymore. I learned how to surf, and the
SaaS was making 1,500 dollars a month.
But churn was high. To earn
money with my software, escape rooms had to
use it. Most didn't. I felt
like on a treadmill: New customer, new churn.
So I offered a yearly plan for 1,999
dollars and got some sales. My
revenue hit 3,000 dollars in early
2020. But I was just running faster on
the treadmill. So I built a new product
called GameWidget: An embedded mini-game on websites to
entertain visitors and offer discount coupons.
Winners of the game get a discount coupon
for the escape rooms. Same market escape
rooms and same strategy
gamification marketing but different
fulfillment. Instead of using the software,
my customers just had to add a script
to their sites and let the magic happen.
I beta-tested the product for 2 months and
the results were impressive: +0.6 percent conversion rate
3 percent is considered great in the industry
I was excited.
Chapter 4. Failing life.
When COVID hit in March 2020, all escape
rooms closed. My revenue went to 0
dollars in a week. I was fortunate to
be in Bali because I met Hugues, who
became my best friend. We spent 6 months
surfing empty waves and talking about life. We
surfed 6-9-foot waves in tandem.
Just like my girlfriend, he never judged me—I
could show him every weird side of my
personality. Thanks to them, I stopped caring
about what others think of me. In the
summer of 2020, my girlfriend and I decided
to get married. We flew back to France.
My Korean parents did too. The wedding was
wonderful. Unfortunately, we couldn't go back
to Bali due to COVID restrictions. We lived
in Paris with my parents and sisters for
1 year. I worked on my previous SaaS
and got it back to 1,000 dollars MRR,
but something was off. I didn't like it
anymore, so I quit. After a few months
of nothingness, I had to start something new.
Anything. So I launched The Golden Plumber
in January 2021. Males often dribble after
going to the toilet, due to the nature
of our engine—as my sister explained she's a
doctor Entrepreneurship at its peak.
I created an info-product
2-page PDF and ran ads
on adult websites. I made 4
dollars in 2 months. I quit,
again. My parents gave me 100,000
dollars as an early legacy. I invested
everything in Tesla in March 2021, when the
stock hit an all-time high. I refused to
use the money for at least 20 years.
I still believe it's not mine. 2
weeks later, my portfolio went down by
minus 36,000 dollars. I was 27 years
old, broke, and living with my parents. A
recurring thought started to echo: I am a
failure… Here's a photo of the four holes
I dug in the wall. On Wednesday, 9th,
June 2021, while drinking a morning coffee in
my bedroom, I started to cry. Sadness
turned to anger, and I dug 4 holes
in the wall. Chapter
5. Overcoming depression. It's
not common to see a 27-year-old boy crying
in his mum's arms on the sofa. But
life isn't like movies. I needed a
change, a big one: Quit
entrepreneurship and get a job.
Within 2 weeks of applying as a software
engineer, I got an interview. At the end,
HR asked: Do you want to say anything
to Tai Lopez? It wasn't written on the
application, but it was a 9,000 dollars a
month job offer to work for Tai Lopez.
I accepted. I started reading.
I thought I hated books because it was
boring in high school. It turned out to
be my favorite activity. My first book was
"Why We Sleep" by Matthew Walker. It
changed my life. I realized I was
tired without knowing it. Fixing my sleep
unlocked more motivation, happiness, and less anxiety.
While I worked for Tai, I also learned
Korean. 1 hour a day, 6 days a
week. 3 months later, I could have a
conversation with my wife. My mood
improved every day. I was growing,
and I finally had a sense of purpose.
In October 2021, we went back home to
Bali A laptop beside the window at
home in Bali. In November, I got
fired. But it didn't matter. I
was so inspired by Pieter Levels building startups
in public that I went back to entrepreneurship.
I had a new dream.
Chapter 6. Just for fun.
When there isn't much happening in your life,
it's hard to find a startup idea. I
was so frustrated with my previous years of
go-big-or-go-home mindset that I needed a simple project
everyone could understand. In December
2021, Mood2Movie was born. A movie
recommendation app based on your mood. It
sounds fancy, but it's just a simple if
mood then movie genre.
This app got 20K+ visitors by going viral
on Hacker News. This project kickstarted
my build-in-public journey. The app is free, so
I could launch it everywhere on Reddit. One
post went viral and got 10K visitors.
So I had somewhat valuable content to share
on Twitter. In 6 months, I launched 7
projects without thinking about business, just for fun.
I learned much about coding, SEO, writing,
launching, and marketing. My Twitter
account reached 1,000 followers in July
2022. Meantime, I ate healthy food,
prioritized sleep, and worked out every day
surfing or skating I also
raised a chick. Here's a photo of
me as a software engineer in 2020, on
the left, and as a solopreneur in 2021,
on the right. Even though I was making
just a few hundred dollars a month, it
was too much fun to give up.
Chapter 7. I fell in love.
In August 2022, my gamified habit tracker, Habits
Garden, was making about 200 dollars a month,
so I went all-in. But
I'm a product-obsessed developer. I don't
like marketing. Side-project
marketing saved me: Ship free tools to promote
a paid one. For instance, I launched
VisualizeHabit—a free tool to visualize the compound
effect of tiny habits. I plugged Habits
Garden, and it brought 30,000 visitors in 2
months. If you read 5 minutes/day
for 1 year, you'll finish 6 books!
For a side project to work, I had
to be good at launching. I started to
make fun launch videos. People enjoyed and
shared them, creating a viral loop. Each side
project grew my Twitter following and brought decent
traffic. Here's a photo from my skit for
the launch of ByeDispute. Thanks to
side-project marketing and launch videos, Habits
Garden reached 10,000 users in January 2023.
Users requested a mobile app. I
had no idea how to code it, but
I tried. After 14 days with the help
of my friend Martin, Habits Garden was live
on the App Store and the Play Store.
It was making 700 dollars a month.
Not bad, but not worth 6 months of
my life. I fell in love with the
wrong product.
Chapter 8. Back on the grind.
Early 2023, I sold a micro-startup
I built in 2021. It was making
80 dollars a month and was
acquired for 4,300 dollars. I
had stories to tell. My Twitter account grew
by about 50 followers a day. But I
was still not making enough to cover my
cheap lifestyle. So I did the 2021
strategy again: Ship startups like a
madman. But this time, I applied some rules:
No free plan. Only
painkiller product. Move on if no
product-market fit. I built 8
startups in 8 months. 6 made
money. 2 paid the bills.
Ship fast, launch viral, repeat.
In July 2023, I was making about 3,000
dollars a month. 60 percent of my
revenue came from MakeLanding, an AI landing
page generator. I tried to grow it but
failed. I didn't use the product, and I
didn't care about the market. I just built
the startup out of AI FOMO. In August
2023, my whole family flew to South Korea,
where my wife and I remarried. It was
wonderful. Here's a photo of my wife and
me in traditional Korean wedding clothes.
Chapter 9. Product-market fit, finally.
Holidays are magic. When I left
for Korea in August 2023, my head was
full of questions. When I came back, it
was obvious: I must build a business for
customers I care about. So I quit all
my faceless AI projects and focused on products
I'd use. I sold my AI landing page
generator for 35,000 dollars and my habit
tracker for 10,000 dollars. It gave me
time and clarity. I wrote about the
process and the outcome. On September
1st, I launched ShipFast, a NextJS
boilerplate to ship startups fast. I
packed 2 years of shipping knowledge in a
GitHub repo. ShipFast diagram showing the
technologies and features in the boilerplate.
I told my wife we'd be lucky if
we made 100 dollars with it. By the
end of the month, ShipFast made 40,000 dollars.
I was blown away. It's hard to
describe product-market fit, but when it hits, it's
clear. I kept adding features while
tweeting about it. I received tons of testimonials
from customers who made their first 1 dollar
online thanks to the boilerplate. I was
happy. I also launched ByeDispute: A
no-code tool to prevent Stripe chargebacks.
In November, my revenue hit 65,400
dollars a month at a 91 percent
margin and 0 employees. By the end
of 2023, ShipFast alone made almost 200,000
dollars in total revenue. It felt so
good to be financially rewarded for my last
7 years of work. Here's an old
Stripe screenshot, taken on December
17th, 2023.
Chapter 10. Rat race.
I started a YouTube channel in 2024.
Thumbnails from Marc's YouTube channel. The
videos made ShipFast hit 133,000
dollars in monthly revenue in April
2024. The YouTube channel quickly grew to 100K
followers because I had a story and numbers
to back it up. This made me overconfident.
I started to believe I was Alex Hormozi
for developers, so I doubled down on content
and info-products. People kept asking how
I learned to code under my videos, so
I built CodeFast. It took 9 months
working 6 hours a day. It made 100,000
dollars in 2 days. CodeFast's launch
video was my favorite part of building this
product. My mood was negatively
affected by the ups and downs in revenue.
One month I could make 120 thousand dollars,
the next 40 thousand dollars. I told myself
it's stupid to stress because I'm still making
very good money, but it's hard to ignore
degrowth. I wish I could tell you I
was happy making 1.2 million dollars by the
end of 2024, but realistically, it felt like
a rat race where I had to work
harder and harder to keep the numbers up.
Chapter 11. First love.
I launched DataFast in October 2024.
I connected Stripe with web analytics to find
out my best marketing channels. It
reached 300 dollars MRR in 2 weeks.
The revenue was ridiculous compared to CodeFast,
but it saved me. After spending 9 months
making videos, I felt happiness finally building
features people could use and touch. I know
it sounds weird, but that's my happy place.
I realized I had to go back to
my first love: building apps out of curiosity,
not revenue opportunity.
Chapter 12. Builder mindset.
When I started building in public, I had
one goal in mind: 1 startup per month.
I drifted in 2024, but I was
back in 2025. I built BioAge,
SuperShrimp, and many other little projects that
never really made money, and my overall revenue
went down, but it didn't matter. I was
having fun again. The SuperShrimp website
with the headline Fix Your Posture. I also
prioritized other aspects of life and worked less.
My wife and I travelled the world: New
Zealand, South Korea, Bali, South Africa, Greece.
And I started running and lifting weights.
Chapter 13. 10 percent rule.
I launched TrustMRR on
October 30th, 2025. 24 hours
later, it was making 20,000 dollars a month
in ad placements. I vibe-coded the
platform in 6 hours. The TrustMRR
startup leaderboard and advertising placements.
The hype died the next month, so I
started building verticals to keep the project afloat.
After 10 failures, the startup marketplace
took off in January 2026. Someone made an
offer to acquire TrustMRR for 1 million
dollars. I rejected the offer.
7 months later: 164
founders got acquired. 200K
people visit the site every month. and
I've made almost 400,000 dollars.
I've documented TrustMRR's journey here.
Meanwhile, I added features to DataFast, and it
kept growing. As I'm writing this
in September 2026, it's now at
30,831 dollars MRR and about 7
percent churn. Here's a photo
of the DataFast chart, at about thirty thousand
eight hundred thirty-one dollars MRR. I
launched Stalkr in August 2026 and got my
first customers. It's doing 223
dollars MRR, which is very tiny compared to
my other products, but it doesn't matter!
I build tools for myself, and I'm having
fun. Stalkr is how I find testimonials,
feature ideas, and bug reports for my products.
I see a recurring pattern: I have no
idea what's going to work. ShipFast and
TrustMRR blew up overnight.
DataFast was slow and steady. My
other 30 startups never really made money.
90 percent of my 36 startups failed.
And that's ohhh kay.
My goal is to build stuff that makes
me happy, even if it doesn't make money.
Chapter 14. Starting over.
Back in 2016, when I started, I believed
I would make it. If I had known
it would take 7 years of failure, I
probably would never have started.
That's why I'm stupidly optimistic.
I don't think in years. I don't dream
big. I think in weeks.
I build tiny projects fast. And
I quit even faster. That's how I
wake up happy, enjoy the journey, and eventually
build life-changing projects. If you've been
following the journey, thank you. You've given my
posts a sense of purpose, which has kept
me going, and I'm very grateful for this.
I root for you and your projects. ❤️
PS. Here's my little portfolio of
everything I built